Office of the Vice-President, Finance and Administration fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Committees, 1966 - 1984; F-28-7; 2.34 m of textual records
  - Interior Program Planning Committee, 1977 - 1979; F-28-7-16; 26 cm of textual records
    - Follow-up Meetings, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - School of Active Health Sciences - Minutes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-13 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - School of Applied Sciences - Minutes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-14 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - School of Education - Minutes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-15 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - School of Fine Arts - Minutes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-16 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - School of Humanities - Minutes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-17 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - School of Management Studies - Minutes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-18 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - School of Resource Management - Minutes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-19 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - School of Small Technology - Minutes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-20 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Basic Elements: School of Excellence, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-21 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - B.C. Planning Bodies: Non-Metropolitan degree Completion Programs, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-22 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Costing: School Prototypes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-23 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Discussion Paper: Model for the Development of Degree Completion Programs, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-24 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Distance Education, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-25 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Interior University Programs Board, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-26 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Overall Plan, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-27 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Section 1: Why a Needs Assessment?, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-28 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Interior Program Planning Committe Recommendations - Final Report, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-29 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Interior Program Planning Committee Papers, 1978 - 1979; F-28-7-16-0-30 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Proposal for A School for the Arts, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-31 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
  - Classification Advisory Committee, 1974 - 1975; F-28-7-17; 13 cm of textual records
    - Terms of Reference, 1974; F-28-7-17-0-1 (Archival box - small 28-41)
    - Minutes, 1974 - 1975; F-28-7-17-0-2 (Archival box - small 28-41)
    - Papers, 1974 - 1975; F-28-7-17-0-3 (Archival box - small 28-41)
  - Vice-Presidents' Meetings, 1973; F-28-7-18; 1 cm of textual records
    - Minutes and Support Papers, 1973; F-28-7-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-43)
- Printed materials, 1967 - 1982; F-28-8; 17 cm of textual records
  Series consists of printed materials relating to reviews and proposals concerning various administrative units and programs. It includes reports prepared by administrative units or external consultants.
  - Ancillary Services - Central Stores Review, 1973 - 1974; F-28-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
  - Audio Visual Centre - Reorganization of Audio Visual Services and The Library Audio Visual Centre, 1967 - 1968; F-28-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
  - Centre for the Arts - Proposal for Further Development of the Centre for the Arts, 1981; F-28-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
  - Centre for the Arts - 1981 Annual Report of the Simon Fraser Gallery, 1982; F-28-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
  - Comptroller General - Statement of Financial Condition, 1968; F-28-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-24)
  - Departments of Recreation, Kinesiology, Athletics, and Education - Professional Certificate Programs for Physical Education Teachers, Recreation Specialists, and Althletics Coaches, 1976; F-28-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-24)
  - Landrey, Ann - A Report on Student Employment at Simon Fraser University, 1973; F-28-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-24)
  - McLellan, Robert and Co. Ltd. - Report on Proposed Funicular Railway, 1971; F-28-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-24)
  - Personnel - Pension Plans, Minimum Planning Budget, Supervisory and Management Training, and Fee Survey Report, 1969 - 1972; F-28-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-24)
  - Personnel - Modified Work Week, Group Life and Long Term Disability Insurance, and Development of a Compensation Program, 1973 - 1981; F-28-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-24)
  - Physical Plant and Planning - Arthur Erickson Architects - Purpose and Justification, Stores Security, Planning for S.F.U, 1973 - 1975; F-28-8-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-24)
  - Stead, Meehan, Haggman - Supervisory and Management Training..., 1972; F-28-8-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-24)
  - Vice-President, Administration - Overview of Administrative Departments: A Report for New Members of the Board of Governors, 1979 - 1981; F-28-8-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 28-24)
  - Woods, Gordon and Co. - Trimester Cost Study Vol. 1, 1972; F-28-8-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 28-24)